Guide to the Department of Athletics, Yale University, Records Documenting Football
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Department of Athletics, Yale University, records documenting football
1853-2004
RU 141
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
50.39
(66 boxes)
The records consist of scrapbooks, memorabilia, correspondence, coaches files and manuals, a ledger, and printed material documenting football at Yale, including George D. Vaill's "Instructions to Competitors" and a videotape of a NBC Nightly News segment concerning the 100th Yale-Harvard football game. Records of coaches Paul L. Veeder and Carm Coza are also included.
Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-B (YRG 38-B), Records documenting specific sports at Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is partially restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of scrapbooks, memorabilia, correspondence, coaches files and manuals, a ledger, and printed material documenting football at Yale, including George D. Vaill's "Instructions to Competitors" and a videotape of a NBC Nightly News segment concerning the 100th Yale-Harvard football game. Records of coaches Paul L. Veeder and Carm Coza are also included.
College sports; Football; Scrapbooks; Videotapes; Vaill, George D.; Yale University Athletic Association; Yale University -- Football; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics
- Y football certificate awarded to John L. Miller, 1921; Accession 1975-A-026
  - Y football certificate awarded to John L. Miller (1924), 1921 (Box 1)
- Records, 1853, 1881-1897, 1915-1916; Accession 1979-A-051
  - Freshmen challenges to Sophomore class, 1853 (Box 1)
  - Yale field corporation - letters dealing with financial concerns, 1881-1897 (Box 1)
  - Yale University Football Association - ledger, 1915-1916 (Box 1)
- NBC Nightly News highlights of 100th Yale-Harvard football game [videorecording], 1983; Accession 1983-A-114
  - NBC Nightly News highlights 100th Yale-Harvard football game, 1983; videotape (VHS) (Box 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
- Statement of football tactics, circa 1912; Accession 1990-A-117
  - Statement of football tactics as set forth in the quarterback regulations, circa 1912 (Box 1)
- Edward H. Coy certificate of induction into the National Football Hall of Fame, 1951; Accession 1994-A-068
  - Edward H. Coy certificate of induction into the National Football Hall of Fame, 1951 (Box 1)
- Instructions to competitors, 1932; Accession 19ND-A-371
  - Instructions to competitors, varsity football competition, George D. Vaill, competitor, 1932 (Box 1)
- Football programs, 1930-1933; Accession 2002-A-117
  - Programs
    - Princeton, 1930 (Box 1)
    - Harvard, 1931 (Box 1)
    - Princeton, 1931 (Box 1)
    - Georgia, 1933 (Box 1)
- Records of Paul L. Veeder as coach for the Yale football team, 1916-1923; Accession 2002-A-123 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Materials relating to 1936 Princeton football game, Accession 2003-A-131 (Box 1)
- Scrapbook of Yale Football Centennial Dinner, 1973; Accession 2004-A-068
  - Scrapbook of Yale Football Centennial Dinner, 1973 (Box 1)
- Writings on the origin and early history of intercollegiate football, 2003-2004; Accession 2004-A-116 (Box 1)
- Yale football team photo collage, 1900; Accession 2004-A-127
  - Yale football team photo collage, 1900 (Box 1)
- Scrapbooks maintained by the football team, 1901-1976; Accession 2006-A-013
  Most scrapbooks are available on microfilm. Patrons must use HM 177 instead of the originals.
  - Scrapbook volumes
    There is no Volume 19 in the accession.
    The scrapbooks volumes are available on microfilm. Patrons must use HM 177 instead of the originals.
    - Volumes 1-2, 1919 (Box 9, Reel 1)
    - Volume 3, 1919-1920 (Box 1, Reel 1)
    - Volume 4, 1921 (Box 2, Reel 2)
    - Volume 5, 1922 (Box 3, Reel 2)
    - Volumes 6-7, 1923-1924 (Box 4, Reel 2)
    - Volumes 8-9, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Reel 3)
    - Volumes 10-11, 1927-1928 (Box 6, Reel 3)
    - Volumes 12-13, 1932-1933 (Box 7, Reel 3)
    - Volume 14, 1934 (Box 8, Reel 4)
    - Volume 15, 1935 (Box 8A, Reel 4)
    - Volume 16, 1936 (Box 11, Reel 4)
    - Volume 17, 1937 (Box 11, Reel 5)
    - Volume 18, 1938, 1940 (Box 12, Reel 5)
    - Volume 20, 1942-1944 (Box 13, Reel 5)
  - 1901 [not microfilmed] (Box 10)
  - 1974-1976 [not microfilmed] (Box 14)
- Records documenting football, 1913-2003; Accession 2006-A-239
  - Dinner to honor Yale football team of 1888, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Completion of Yale Bowl, Circa 1914 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coaches files
    Boxes 4 and 5 are restricted until January 1, 2033.
    - Stats, 1920-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - General Administrative, 1927-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alfred University (game against), 1930 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Awards, 1930-1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1932-1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Press/P.R., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Freshman football, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 150 pound football, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Varsity football, 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Various Dinners, 1937-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Stats, 1943-1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Clinics and Recruitment, 1948-1951 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Harvard, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Stats, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Film Scripts
      - 1950 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - 1960 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Princeton, 1954 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Guide, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Coaches' Pre-Season Meetings, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Film Studies, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Film Studies, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Invitees, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Practice Schedules, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Scripts for Films, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Football, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Gameplan/Plays, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Harvard Game Press Release, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - If Sheets, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Yale Copy, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Statistics, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Scripts, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Film Studies, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Coaches' Pre-Season Meetings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Prospects, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Gameplan, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Invitees, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Movies, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Football, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Practice Schedules, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Invitees, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Football, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Scripts, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Practice Schedule, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - In-Season Film Exchange, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Films, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Coaches' Pre-Season Meetings, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Practice Schedules, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Press/P.R., 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Scripts for Films, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Movies, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Roster: Varsity and Freshmen, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Fitness Tests, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Practice Schedules, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - In-Season Film Exchange, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Invitees, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Football, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Happy Hour Dancing Class, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Tickets, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Invitees, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Practice Schedules, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Scripts for Films, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Football, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - In-Season Film Exchange, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Spring Practice, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Films, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Booth, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - UConn, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Colgate, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Brown, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Cornell, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Dartmouth, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Columbia, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Penn, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Princeton, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Harvard, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Stats, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Awards, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Statistics, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - In-Season Film Exchange, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Invitees, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Practice Schedules, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Ticket Requests, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Football, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Spring Practice, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Film Titles, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Invitees, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Ticket Requests, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Football, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Play by Plays, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Hi-lite Scripts, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Out-Of-Season Films, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Practice Schedules, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - "Y" News Articles, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Spring Practice, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Practice Schedules, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - In-Season Film Exchange, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 111 - 112)
    - Invitees, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Ticket Requests, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Out-Of-Season Film Exchange, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Football, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Dinner, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Out-Of-Season Film Exchange, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Film Exchanges, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Invitees, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Football, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Practice Schedules, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Ticket Requests, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Newsclippings, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 125 - 126)
    - Photos- Madison Beach Club Barbecue, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Press/P.R., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Awards, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Ticket Requests, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Invitees, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Football, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Film Exchanges, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Practice Schedules, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Freshman and J.V. Football, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Film Exchanges, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Invitees, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Freshman Football, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Practice Schedules, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Football, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Freshman Football, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Invitees, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Film Exchange, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Football, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Press/P.R. Stuff, 1972-1986 (Box 4, Folder 145)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1987 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Invitees, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Film Exchanges, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Freshman Football, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Invitees, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Football, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Football Players Labs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Freshman Football, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Film Exchanges, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Football, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Robert G. Anderson Award, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - General Administrative, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Football (Varsity), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Football (Freshmen), 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Football, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Awards, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Kevin Czinger, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Assorted Football, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Season Prospectus, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Harvard/Yale: The Game, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Radio Contracts, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Football: General, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Highlight film, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Y News, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - General Administrative, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Y News, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Spring Practice, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Conditioning Programs, 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - J.V. Referee Evaluations, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Depth Charts, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - General Administrative, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Frosh Football, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Memos, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Pre-Season Arrangements, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - General Administrative, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - J.V. Football, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Freshman Football, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Football: General, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Football: Freshman/Varsity Correspondence, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Chronological File, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Two-A-Day Practice Material, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Football: General, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 189)
    - Game Summaries, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 189A)
    - Season, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 190)
    - Game files
      - Central Connecticut, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 191)
      - Brown, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 192)
      - UConn, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 193)
      - Colgate, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 194)
      - Lafayette, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 195)
      - Dartmouth, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 196)
      - Penn, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 197)
      - Columbia, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 198)
      - Cornell, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 199)
      - Princeton, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 200)
      - Harvard, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 201)
      - Harvard Clippings, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 202)
      - Statistics, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 203)
      - Freshmen, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 204 - 205)
      - General, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 206)
      - Brown, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 207)
      - Lafayette, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 208)
      - Colgate, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 209)
      - UConn, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 210)
      - Dartmouth, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 211)
      - Columbia, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 212)
      - Penn, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 213)
      - Cornell, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 214)
      - Princeton, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 215)
      - Harvard, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 216)
      - Freshmen, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 217)
      - Union College, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 218)
      - Football, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 219)
      - Junior Varsity, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 220)
      - Freshmen, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 221)
      - Brown, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 222)
      - Holy Cross, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 223)
      - UConn, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 224)
      - Fordham, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 225)
      - Dartmouth, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 226)
      - Columbia, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 227)
      - Penn, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 228)
      - Cornell, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 229)
      - Princeton, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 230)
      - Harvard, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Press/P.R., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - General Administrative, undated (Box 5, Folder 233)
  - Coaches Manuals
    - 1966
      - General (Box 6, Folder 234)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 235)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 236)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 237 - 238)
    - 1967
      - General (Box 6, Folder 239)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 240 - 241)
    - 1969
      - General (Box 6, Folder 242)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 243 - 244)
    - 1970
      - General (Box 6, Folder 245)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 246)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 247)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 248 - 249)
    - 1971
      - General (Box 6, Folder 250)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 251)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 252)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 253 - 254)
    - 1976
      - General (Box 6, Folder 255)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 256)
      - Opponents (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - 1977
      - General (Box 6, Folder 258)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 259)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - 1978
      - General (Box 6, Folder 261)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 262)
      - Defense (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - 1979
      - General (Box 6, Folder 264)
      - Offense (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - 1980
      - General (Box 7, Folder 266)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 267)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - 1981
      - General (Box 7, Folder 269)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - 1982
      - General (Box 7, Folder 271)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 272)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - 1983
      - General (Box 7, Folder 274)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 275)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - 1984
      - General (Box 7, Folder 277)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 278)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - 1985
      - General (Box 7, Folder 280)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 281)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - 1986
      - General (Box 7, Folder 283)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - 1988
      - General (Box 7, Folder 285)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 286)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 287 - 288)
    - 1989
      - General (Box 7, Folder 289)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 290)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 291 - 292)
    - 1990
      - General (Box 7, Folder 293)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 294)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 295 - 296)
    - 1991
      - General (Box 7, Folder 297)
      - Offense (Box 7, Folder 298)
      - Defense (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - 1993
      - General (Box 8, Folder 300)
      - Offense (Box 8, Folder 301)
      - Defense (Box 8, Folder 302)
    - 1994
      - General (Box 8, Folder 303)
      - Offense (Box 8, Folder 304)
      - Defense (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - No date
      - Defense (Box 8, Folder 306)
      - Defensive playbook - Carm Coza (Box 8, Folder 307)
      - Quarterback manual (Box 8, Folder 308)
  - Historical material
    - Yale-Harvard 100th game memorabilia, 1983
      - Apparel
        - Hat (Box 9)
        - Polo shirt (Box 9)
        - Sweater (Box 9)
        - T-shirt (Box 9)
      - Barware
        - Cup (plastic) (Box 9)
        - Glass (Box 9)
      - Dinner invitation, 1983 November 18 (Box 9, Folder 309)
      - Newspaper (Box 9, Folder 310)
      - Program (Box 9, Folder 311)
      - Tickets (Box 9, Folder 312)
    - Record of games, 1872-1941 (Box 10, Folder 313)
    - Game and team records, 1889-1954 (Box 10, Folder 313A)
    - Scores, 1872-1944 (Box 10, Folder 314)
    - Yale Football Story manuscript
      - 1825-1878 (Box 10, Folder 315)
      - 1879-1884 (Box 10, Folder 316)
      - 1885-1888 (Box 10, Folder 317)
      - 1889 (Box 10, Folder 318)
      - 1890 (Box 10, Folder 319)
      - 1891-1892 (Box 10, Folder 320)
      - 1893 (Box 10, Folder 321)
      - 1894 (Box 10, Folder 322)
      - 1895 (Box 10, Folder 323)
      - 1892-1896 (Box 10, Folder 324)
      - 1897 (Box 10, Folder 325)
      - 1898 (Box 10, Folder 326)
      - 1899-1901 (Box 10, Folder 327)
      - 1902 (Box 10, Folder 328)
      - 1903-1904 (Box 10, Folder 329)
      - 1905-1907 (Box 10, Folder 330)
      - 1908-1910 (Box 10, Folder 331)
      - 1911-1913 (Box 10, Folder 332)
      - 1914-1915 (Box 10, Folder 333)
      - 1916-1918 (Box 10, Folder 334)
      - 1920-1921 (Box 10, Folder 335)
      - 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 336)
      - 1924-1925 (Box 10, Folder 337)
      - 1927-1928 (Box 10, Folder 338)
      - 1929 (Box 10, Folder 339)
      - 1930 (Box 10, Folder 340)
      - 1931 (Box 10, Folder 341)
      - 1932 (Box 10, Folder 342)
      - 1933 (Box 10, Folder 343)
      - 1934 (Box 10, Folder 344)
      - 1935 (Box 10, Folder 345)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 346)
      - 1938-1939 (Box 10, Folder 347)
      - 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 348)
      - 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 349)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 350)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - Yale-United Way game - New York Giants vs. New York Jets program, 1975 August 24 (Box 10, Folder 352)
    - Letter from Jerry Roscoe to Richard Goldstein describing 1934 Yale vs. Brown football game, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Yale Football Tradition print guide, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Ivy Group Football - stats and press (Box 11, Folder 355)
  - New Haven Gridiron Club program, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 356)
  - Patriot League and Ivy League football stadia guide, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 357)
  - Press (Box 11, Folder 358)
  - Programs
    - Ivy League Football
      - 1983 (Box 11, Folder 359)
      - 1984 (Box 11)
      - 1985 (Box 11)
      - 1987 (Box 11)
      - 1994 (Box 11)
      - 1995 (Box 11)
  - Publications, 1954-2003 (Box 11)
  - Rosters, 1960s-1980 (Box 11, Folder 360)
  - Schedules
    - 1953 (Box 11, Folder 361)
    - 1980 (Box 11)
    - 1994 (Box 11)
  - Scorecard - Harvard, 2003 November 22 (Box 11)
  - Scrapbooks
    - 1934-1935 (Box 12)
    - 1937 (Box 12)
  - Statbooks
    - 1976-1979 (Box 13)
    - 1978-1980 (Box 13)
    - 1984 (Box 13)
    - 1985 (Box 13)
    - 1993 (Box 13)
- Men's football game records, 1952-1980; Accession 2006-A-244
  Includes game summaries, rosters, press lists, and stats.
  - Game records
    - 1952-1953 (Box 1)
    - 1954 (Box 2)
    - 1960 (Box 3–4)
    - 1961 (Box 5)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 6)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 7)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 8)
    - 1964-1966 (Box 9)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 10)
    - 1967 (Box 11)
    - 1968 (Box 12)
    - 1969 (Box 13)
    - 1970 (Box 14)
    - 1971 (Box 15)
    - 1972 (Box 16)
    - 1973 (Box 17)
    - 1974 (Box 18)
    - 1975 (Box 19)
    - 1976 (Box 20)
    - 1977 (Box 21)
    - 1979 (Box 22)
    - 1980 (Box 23)
- Leo Stoutsenberger cartoons created for the Yale Football Newsletter, 1966, 1972, undated; Accession 2006-A-265
  Biographical / Historical
  Leo Stoutsenberger was a professor at the Paier College of Art in Hamden, CT. He rendered several comic strip narratives of Yale football games during the latter half of the 20th Century.
  - Yale-Dartmouth game, 50th anniversary, 1966 (Box 1)
  - Yale-Princeton, 95th game, 1972 (Box 1)
    Depicts actio of 18 November 1972, during Yale Football's centennial season. Of paticular note is Dick Jauron, who went on to play professionally for the Detroit Lions, and was later head coach fo the Chicago Bears.
  - Yale-Cornell, "Stalemat at Ithaca," Yale 0 Cornell 0, undated (Box 1)
- Memento program and score care, Yale-Harvard football game, 1893 November 25; Accession 2008-A-187
  - Memento program and score care, Yale-Harvard football game, 1893 November 25 (Box 1)
- Yale-Princeton football game train time table (New York, New Haven and Hartford Railroad Co.), 1903 November 6; Accession 2011-A-011 (Box 1)